MAJID REZA SEPANJ

DoB: August 18, 1977 | Tehran, Iran | (+98)912-277-0795 | MadjidSepanj@Gmail.com

Summary

Proactive and highly skilled Programmer and Software Project Manager with 22 years' track record in the field of Information and Technology. Areas of expertise include analysis, design and development of Windows and Web based software. A team player who works collaboratively, and effectively communicates with all levels of staff. Eager to apply my professional programming skill in Microsoft in challenging position.

Academic Education

Islamic Azad University - Tehran Markaz Branch, Tehran, Tehran Province Bachelor Degree in Applied Mathematics, Graduated May 2002

Employment History

Pasargad Technology Leaders, Tehran, Tehran Province

Production Manager, September 2013 - Present

The company is active in the field of launching organizational portals and developing modules and software in DNN environment, a Persian DNN reference in Iran. Responsibilities include designing, managing, and programming software projects.

Contributed to the following projects as:

- Programmer and Project Manager of the management system for workers of Fruit & Vegetables Market
- Programer of a contractor management system for a procurement company affiliated with the Meli Bank
- Designer and Project Manager of Section B licensing system for travel agencies affiliated with Cultural Heritage, Handicrafts and Tourism Organization of Iran
- Designer and Project Manager of a performance analysis system for the members of the Islamic Consultative Assembly
- Designer and Project Manager of a hyper market system for the Presidential Air Force
- Designer and Project Manager of a management system for workers of Waste Management Organization of Tehran Municipality
- Designer and Project Manager of a management system for workers of Organization of Tehran Municipality Parks
- Designer and Project Manager of a travel guide and metro suppliers system
- Designer and Project Manager of Irtoya online sale and product management
- Designer, Programmer, and Project Manager of arbitration system of Tehran Municipality festivals
- Designer and Project Manager of coontractor management system for Iran Power Network Management Company
- Designer and Project Manager of Building Management System (BMS) software
- Designer and Project Manager of Learning Management System (LMS) software
- Designer and Project Manager of Education Management Information System (EMIS)
- Designer and Project Manager of Business Process Management System (BPMS)

Rayavaran Tose'e Company, Tehran, Tehran Province

Production Manager & December 2017 - December 2017

The company was the largest hospital software developer active in the field of software projects design, management, and implementation.

Contributed to the following projects as:

- Designer, Manager, and Programmer of lab software project
- Designer and Programmer of pharmacy software project
- Progarmer of integrated information system of hospital

- Designer and Programmer of accounting, warehousing, rollcalling, wages, procurement, application management, equipment mobilization, secretary, and property software package
- Designer and Programmer of drug information and interaction

Barin Choob Company, Tehran, Tehran Province

Hardware Administor - Software Designer & Earny; Programmer, March 2005 - July 2007

The company is the largest importer of machinery and raw materials of the wood industry in Iran. Responsibilities include providing and maintaining hardware and network equipment, maintaining existing software and databases, and designing, managing, and implementing the software required by the Brin Group. Contributed to the following projects as:

- Designer and Programmer of web-based personnel Information and wages software
- Designer and Programmer of after-sales services software
- Designer and Programmer of order placement software
- Designer and Programmer of Barin Group web-design project

Deputy Traffic Police Office (NAJA), Tehran, Tehran Province

Network & Dril 2002 - March 2004

Responsibilities include:

- consulting on the selection and provision of network and hardware equipment
- Periodic maintenance of network and hardware equipment
- Launching some of the first deployment centers out of Traffic Police department as the early Police +10 services

Professional Projects

As a programmer, designer, and project manager concluded contracts with different organizations and implemented various types of hardware and software projects in collaboration with a strong team of software and hardware specialists. Some of the projects are:

- Sales and reservation and CRM software for travel agencies
- Electronic services system of Hormozgan Free zones
- Complaints system for Hajj and Pilgrimage Organization
- A system for recording papers and dessertation published by Islamic Azad University at the national level and awarding system
- Sale management, design and production software in printing industry
- After-sales services software for KWC company

Core Abilities

- Software project management
- Programming
- VB6
- VB.NET
- C#
- ASP.NET
- TSQL and MS SQL Server
- ADO.NET and Entity Framework
- Web API
- LINO
- Crystal Report
- Stimulsoft
- DotNetNuke
- Xamarin
- Software design and analysis

Languages

English Persian

